# **TRONG-NHAN NGUYEN**

(+84) 964 915 950 | tr.nhan39@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/trnhan39/ | Dist. 1 Ho Chi Minh City



# PROFILE

A young and energetic professional major in International Relations, aiming to build a successful career in Marketing. With two years of experience in Pharma Marketing & Communications, I have proactively taken on challenges in various roles, including brand communications, campaign execution, events organization, platform operation, projects management. I seek opportunities in International-related environments to exceed my possibilities and create meaningful impact on both the organization and my personal development.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### **DKSH Vietnam**

**JUL 2024 - PRESENT** 

Marketing Assistant | Marketing Omni Healthcare (Report to Associate Director)

Highlight projects: Pharmacies Engagement, Comedomed Launching, 2024 HCMC Dermatology Conference, HCPs Online Campaign, E-Platform Renovation.

- Assisted PM/MM in developing marketing campaigns for key brands, including strategy planning, channel & brand communication planning, and deliverables execution (Product Technical Book, KV, Landing Page, Banners, Content, Design, etc.)
- Managed and maintained brand guidelines across all brand assets to ensure consistency in public communications, social media, internal training, and vendor material. Planned, designed and executed all the Brands materials for AWO activities.
- Worked with agencies to develop & deliver Brands assets, POSM and Promotion activities for FY Campaigns, new product launching.
- Successfully launched and marketed new products to target audiences, strengthening brand recognition and awareness by boosting brand visibility in offline (retail, H&B chains, Sales & Trade Team) and online (E-commerce, social media, KOLs livestream)
- Led Online Visibility & Merchandising Renovation Project for all brands, including developing a new brand identity, managing product listings, promotion schemes, and banners, and worked directly with H&B chains (Hasaki, Watsons, etc) to update brands' online visuals.
- Supported Brand Manager to follow-up & update documents, payment, accrual process.
- Organized and led training sessions for BAs, Internal Sales force, covering key aspects such as pathogenesis, unique selling points (USP), and brand messaging.
- Conducted pharmacy engagement activities, including pharmacy product reviews activation, to strengthen product positioning, deep dive in pharmacist insights as well as maintain good relationships
- Developed and executed in-store marketing activations to increase foot traffic and drive product sales key contact for internal & external stakeholders.
- Conducted market visits to gather field insights, carry out research, and analyze competitor activities for strategic alignment.
- Streamlined internal systems processes and documentation for marketing activities by liaising with multiple departments, improving team collaboration and reducing turnaround time

### MAY 2023 - MAY 2024

# Sanofi Vietnam | B.U Vaccines

(Report to Omni-Channel Manager)

# Brand Executive - Vaccines Marketing Team

- Highlight projects: Flu Festive Campaign, Baby Dragon Campaign.
- Supported PM/MM in developing and implementing medical information into branded/ unbranded materials (POSM, OOH, etc.)
- Developed and directly monitored communication contents on multi-channel (social platforms, TV News, KOLs, SEM, Website) and online PR press (VNexpress, Dân Trí, Tuổi Trẻ, Kênh14, etc.)
- Successfully executed over 40 marketing events with various scales, raising disease awareness and providing medical value for more than 20,000 healthcare professionals nationwide.
- Analyzed post-campaign data and market reports to drive improvement actions and key learnings for future projects.

# Digital Executive - Vaccines Marketing Team

- Highlight projects: HVTC Website Renovation, HCPs Website Launching, Zalo ZNS Messages, Rep Trigger Email Intergrated
- In charge of all technical issues and ad hoc management of the BU's digital assets.
- Directly managed website renovation project from master sitemap, content development, layout design and user experience. Conducted website testing and troubleshooting across different browsers and devices → Accelerates the project timeline from 1 year to 4 months.
- Coordinated different stakeholders both internal (brand team, procurement) and external (agencies, health associations) to align budget, finalize quotation, and get approval processes.

# EDUCATION

University of Social Sciences and Humanities
- HCMC National University (USSH)
International Relations | 2020 - 2024

# LANGUAGE

**English: Fluent** 

# KEY COMPETENCIES

Microsoft Office Suite Outlook Canva
Presentation Researching Planning
Stakeholder Management Communication
Data Management Content Creation
Creative Mindset Project Management
Campaign Execution Critical Evaluation

# REFERENCES

### Sanofi Vietnam

1. Mr. Luong Minh Thuyet

Title: Country Head - ASEA Partner Markets

Phone: 077 2477192

Email: luongthuyet@gmail.com

2.Mrs. Lona

Title: Marketing Manager, Sanofi Vietnam

Phone: +84 91 4165135

Email: thikimloan.dinh@sanofi.com

3.Mrs. Pham Thi Diem Hang

Title: Omnichannel Manager, Vaccines SEA & India

Phone: +84 97 5441828

Email: thidiemhang.pham@sanofi.com

### **DKSH Vietnam**

1. Mrs. Dang Hoang Uyen Thy

Title: Associate Director, Omni Channel Sales & Marketing

Phone: 0944300884

2.Mrs. Ngo Hoang Ha Linh

Title: Senior Manager, Product ManagemenT

Phone: 0903061291

Email: linh.hoangha.ngo@dksh.com

# Marketing Assistant | OTC - Omnichannel Sales & Marketing

# HCMC's Dermatology Conference





### Digital Campaign





Booth New Product Launching





Trade Scheme Design





Seeding box

In-store Activation







### Online Brand Visibility (Renovation Project)













# **Brand & Digital Executive**









⊕ a | evavn 💝 🕮 THANH MIEN 12/04/2024 08:00 (94/1+7 Tiêm chủng chậm lịch, không đủ liểu, nguy cơ trẻ mắc 6 bệnh truyển nhiễm nguy hiểm An NgN Các ca bệnh họ gà tặng mạnh ở nhiều nơi, cần làm gì

Master KV





Hệ miền dịch của trẻ nhỏ còn non nới nên rất để mắc bệnh, đặc biệt là 6 bệnh truyền nhiệm nguy hiểm hàng đầu gốm viêm gan B, bạch hấu, họ gà, uốn vấn, bại liệt và bệnh do vi khuẩn Hib. Tiềm vắc xin trẻ

Trẻ cảng nhỏ cảng để mắc ho gà và diễn tiến nặng. Trong bối cảnh số ca họ gà tăng trên có nước, tiêm ngừa đủ liểu - đúng lịch là cách phòng bênh hiệu quá cho trẻ,

để phòng bệnh cho trẻ nhỏ?

Display Ads in Grab App

Zalo Inbox Ads

OOH Advertising

PR Articles Post on Presses











Master KV

Banner & Landing Page

Hero Video







**Disease Awareness Website Renovation** 

Chào mừ ng bạn đến với Campus Sanofi Việt Nam

Tim hiểu thêm về thông tin khoa học

Sanofi Campus Website

# MarCom Activities













